mystream.la 2014-03-03

# Videos for every moment — Mystream.la

  * Skip to navigation (n)
  * Skip to content (c)
  * Skip to footer (f)

  * Home
  * Earn Money _(6)_
  * [Blog](https://blog.mystream.la/) _(7)_
  * Privacy Policy _(2)_
  * Terms of Service _(3)_
  * Report Abuse _(4)_
  * Help _(1)_
  * Contact Us _(5)_

  * Sign In
  * Sign Up

English

  * Privacy Policy _(6)_
  * Terms of Service _(7)_
  * Copyright _(8)_

  * Back to Top
  * Collection and Storage
  * Use
  * Deletion or change
  * Global Policy

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy policy provides guidelines about the procedures of the collection, use and disclosure of your information. The service offered by myStream (which is hereinafter referred to as ‘our services’) can be accessed through our official website Mystream.la. You can also access it through APIs, applications on devices as well as through third parties. In this policy, the term ‘Device’ refers to any computer that is used for accessing the service offered by myStream including tablet, laptop, desktop, mobile phone, etc. This privacy policy governs your access to our services, regardless of the way in which it is accessed. By accepting to use our services you are deemed to have consented to the process of collecting, transferring, storing, disclosing, and the other uses as described in this policy. The term ‘Information’ is used in this policy to describe all the various forms of information, content and data as described here below. 

## Collection and Storage

While our services are up and running we may collect and store various types of information including the following: 

Private Datas: after creating an account, it is only your password and email that is saved in our database. However, we can also collect other private datas such as your billings information, your name, email address, etc based on the information you’ve provided to us. Through your email, you can also grant us access to your other email addresses, file sharing, or to social network. We collect this information once you approve the same. It will be done according to the directions that you provide.

Files: after uploading your files on our myStream Service, we will do the collection, storage, securing and their compression. Instead of storing twice a file, we may associate part or the entire existing file to another file that is added to your account on myStream.

Log Data: if you use our Service, we will automatically record some information stored in your device and its softwares as well as activity. Some examples of the data that we can collect includes the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your device, type of browser, the sites that you visited before our website, local preferences, your mobile carrier, information you search and find on our website, ID No. associated with the device that you use, time and date stamps of your transactions, information of system of configuration, the metadata that concerns your Files, and other such interactions with the services that we provide.

Cookies: myStream may use cookies to collect some certain information from those who visit our site. Cookie can be described as some small data file transferred to your device. Many websites that you visit everyday use cookies because it enables the owners or administrators of website to collect important information that may help them improve services. Session ID cookies use allows our website administrators to enable your account’s features. You can stop accepting cookies by adjusting the settings of your browser options. You may also set your browser such that it prompts you before it accept cookie from the websites that you visit. However, some aspects of our service can only be accessed and used if your browser settings are such that you readily accept cookies

## Use

When you accept or begin using our services we may collect your personal information. We will use the information we have collected to identify you. There are various ways in which myStream may use the personal information it has collected. These are as follows:

Improving our services

Administering use of our services

Gaining better understanding of your interest and needs

Personalizing your experience, and sometimes for offering product announcements.

To secure your data we may have to step in it but we’ll not look at it. At anytime, you can unsubscribe from our communications by simply following the instructions we provide in our newsletters. You can also unsubscribe by updating the information of your account settings. 

Geo-Location: Sometimes, we may use the information we’ve collected from your device (e.g. the IP address) so as to find its exact location.

Analyses: Cookies and logging make it possible for us to collect some necessary information which may sometimes be related to the Personal Information. There are various ways in which this information can be used for example:

Increasing the functionality of our Services

Controlling how our services are used, and for technical administration of our services

We use only Google Analytics from now onwards as well as from the date in which this policy came to effect.

## Deletion or change

By changing account settings, registered users can delete, update or review their personal information. If it is so required by law, your information’s copies may be kept by us.

Deletion: Your information will be retained for as long as your account remains active. At any time, you may go to the settings option of your account and delete your account in its entirety if you wish to do so. If you delete your account, we will never use the information you have provided to us in the provision of our services. We are allowed to use and retain information if doing so is necessary for resolution of disputes, enforcement of our agreements or for compliance with our obligations under the law. However, the process of deleting the information stored or contained in your account from our servers may take some time. Also, after deletion there may be existence of some of the backed up versions. In addition to the foregoing, there will be no deletion from our servers of those files common with you and other users.

## Global Policy

Security: Security of the information that you provide to us is something that we care very much about. We use SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology to encrypt the sensitive information provide to us. Further, we follow standards that are generally accepted so as to protect information that you submit to us. However, it should be noted as matter of fact that there is no 100% secure electronic storage or transmission method. In consequence, there can be no absolute guarantee of security. Any questions as regards security measures on our website can be channeled to us through [security@mystream.la](mailto:security@mystream.la).

Policy towards children: We offer our services only to persons aged 13 years or older. In essence, we don’t collect personal information from persons less than 13 years old. Guardians or parents who become aware that without their consent the child has provided Personal information should inform us of the same at [privacy@mystream.la](mailto:privacy@mystream.la), and we will take reasonably quick action to ensure that such information is deleted from our files.

Changes to this Privacy Policy: We may amend this Privacy Policy as we deem fit and necessary. We will endeavor to provide notice to all concerned if we reasonably believe that the proposed changes to this policy may significantly reduce their rights. In other circumstances, we may provide notice of proposed change to this policy. After the proposed changes have been effected, your continued use of our services will be deemed to signify your consent that you accept to be bound the Privacy Policy in its revised form.

How to contact us: Do you have any questions as regards our privacy policy? If yes, send an email with all your questions at [privacy@mystream.la](mailto:privacy@mystream.la).
